Translated by Releska
If you're happy, you won't be with me, so I'll be with you for the rest of your life.
I'm happy.
Is that the rest of your mom's?
Yes, I'm happy.
I'm happy that you're happy that you're happy.
I'm happy.
Hey!
Look!
I'll read it.
I'm sorry, but can you read it?
Yes, I can read it.
Please come to my store as soon as possible.
I'm waiting for you.
I want to introduce you to Rukamukawa.
I'm happy to meet you!
I'm happy that you can meet you!
Rocky?
I keep getting the rest of my Japanese foodص.
That's why I'm happy!
How do you do I'm happy that you can get food from that restaurant again?
If you're happy, I'll be with you for the rest of your life.
I'll be the boss of the company next time!
I forgot about that!
Stop it!
I'm saying that I'm the boss of Muka Muka-san!
Then I'll be the boss?
Yes, I'll be the boss of the company next time!
Hmm...
Are you okay, Muka Muka?
Muka Muka and Yamaneko!
Muka Muka, you have to be calm, so don't be so impulsive!
Yeah, I'm not so scared to eat.
I'm just thinking about my own.
Muka Muka, you're like a kid.
Really?
Yeah, I'm a little...
If I'm too slow, I'll be able to help Yamaneko-san!
I'm okay!
But I thought it was a good idea to be called a demon.
I think it would be a good idea to be called a demon.
I'm waiting for you.
I'm going to take a walk.
Let's go.
Take care.
Let's eat a lot.
It might be a good idea to go back.
What's going on?
I wonder if it's a bad idea to walk.
It's not a good idea to walk.
It's a good idea to walk.
It's okay.
I'm going to take a walk.
I can't believe it.
But is it really?
It's a good idea to take a walk.
Really?
If you think about it, it's a good idea to walk.
It's a good idea to walk.
I see.
Let's go to the next one.
It's a good idea.
Watch out.
Let's go.
I'm going to walk.
Thank you.
Don't worry.
Let's meet again.
Okay!
Okay...
Okay, okay!
I wonder if I can really get on the horse?
Oh...
Yes...
I'm in trouble!
It's got to be a foothold!
It's a foothold!
I'm in trouble!
I'll make it!
Oh, it's a foothold!
I see!
I see.
Let's go to this place.
Wait! Wait!
I can't see anyone.
What are you doing, Kumka-san?
You're going to get mad at me, right?
If you don't let me go, I'll be fine!
What's the matter?
Alright, let's go!
I'll take the sea, and then I'll take the sea!
Sen-san, hurry up!
I told you to do it!
I'm sure you're right.
I'm sure you're right!
Wait, I'll be right back.
I'll be right back.
It's a mission!
It's a mission to achieve the mission!
I'll make it a mission!
I'll take the sea, and then I'll take the sea!
It's a mission to achieve the mission!
Wow, I see!
I'm sure you're right!
I'll make it a mission!
Should I remember?
Oh~!
Huh?
I don't want to say that!
It's quite different from the others, isn't it?
Ah! That's a lie!
But where did the other people go?
I'll be right back, I'll be right back.
If I could have come to a good place like this,
it might be dangerous for the other people too, right?
Uiiba, are you sure?
I'm not sure.
I told you I wanted to go to the other side of Yamaneko-san,
but I'm not sure.
Uiiba...
Yeah, that's true.
Now, let's go inside.
Wow!
From now on, this is the room where Muka-muka is.
Muka-muka...
If there's something you don't care about,
why do you say that?
Yofu-kun, let's go to the other side of Yofu-kun.
Wow!
Muka-muka...
I'm still going to the other side of Yofu-kun.
Yeah, Muka-muka...
I see.
Muka-muka is still going to the other side of Yofu-kun.
Yeah, Muka-muka is still going to the other side of Yofu-kun, isn't she?
I'm sure she'll be right back.
I got it.
Let's go eat now.
Muka-muka...
Muka-muka is still going to the other side of Yofu-kun, isn't she?
That's Muka-muka's room, isn't she?
Let's go inside.
Anyway, let's check it out.
No, we're kids.
Yeah, let's go inside.
Yeah, that's right.
Just stop at my room.
Okay, I got it.
Muka-muka is probably right here.
If you're in the room, you'll get scared.
Let's go inside.
Sorry, we're in the other side of Yofu-kun.
J-J, that's good.
We'll be right back.
Muka-muka is probably right here.
I don't know.
Muka-muka was getting bigger than before.
It's a bit too late, it's too late.
M-Muka-muka, where are you?
M-Muka, sorry.
What's going on?
Is it...
you're totally into this?
He's a smart.
Muka Muka 0.
I'll be gonna hand him over to my sister.
That's dumb.
Hey!
I'm your assistant!
Hey, will you do this?
Hey, where is the other guy? He's looking for him!
He's looking for him!
Oh, no!
He looks so fun!
Yes.
How do you like this place?
I don't want to be like this.
Muka Muka.
I want to be like this too.
I'm going to die here.
I see.
You don't have anything to do?
I'm sorry.
I don't have to worry about Muka Muka.
I came here to buy it.
Don't worry.
Muka Muka can fly and fly.
Yes.
The Tylenine...
Muka Muka is strong.
I very loves a strong guy who doesn't dare to swear.
I will do my best.
How are you going to look centered?
My watch is wide open.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Where have you been?
No, no, no, no!
No!
I've been able to eat it!
It's very delicious!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Right in the water!
It's so delicious!
A dramatic render with a Buzzleaf
It's a distraction
I don't know if it's true, but I'm still in love with you.
Even though I'm still in love with you, I'm still in love with you.
I'm going to lose my mind.
Let's go! Let's go!
Let's go to the tomorrow morning
Let's go!
Where are you going?
Mr. Muka, are you going to the park?
Look at this beautiful place.
There are plenty of delicious food.
Mr. Muka, if you wish to eat something, please give it to me.
I'll give it to you.
Mr. Muka, what are you doing?
Mr. Muka, stop it.
Mr. Muka, what's wrong?
What's wrong?
Mr. Muka!
Good.
I'll give it to you.
What?
Mr. Muka, what's wrong?
It's just like that.
Please give it to Mr. Muka.
Please give it to me.
I can't think of anything else.
Sorry.
Mr. Muka.
Mr. Muka!
Please give it to Mr. Muka.
Mr. Muka, you're a cute person.
Mr. Muka, you give it to Mr. Muka.
I saw something suspicious.
Even if theImager leaves a message, I'll give it to you.
Mr. Muka, what's wrong?
Is it true that you're making it up again?
I have nothing to make.
I was able to live in a lonely place, but I feel like I can live in a lonely lonely place.
I'm also a teacher.
I met Muka Muka at that time.
I was able to live with Muka Muka Muka at that time.
How wonderful.
It's not like that! Do you have any idea about Uiba's feelings?
Yes, I'm Oroka.
I'm really sorry.
But I can't give up on Muka Muka Muka.
I don't have anything to eat in a warm place like this.
I'll give it to you.
I'll give you Muka Muka Muka.
I'll never forgive you.
After a year, this island has changed the world.
It's time to go back to this sea again.
A year?
I'm begging you.
I'll do my best, Muka Muka.
It's really good, Uiba.
It's only a year.
I want to live with my mom as well.
I'll be able to live with Muka Muka.
It's not like that.
It's been a year.
I'm not forgetting about Muka Muka.
I'm not forgetting about Muka.
If I can do this, I'll give you Muka Muka's drink and be happy.
But before Muka Muka comes back,
I'll be able to go back to the rest of the world.
That time is that time.
Uiba!
Now, let's go back to the island.
Muka Muka!
Let's go to the island.
Now, Uiba.
Muka Muka.
It's a wonderful night.
I wonder if that's right.
Really?
Muka Muka!
What's wrong?
That's...
Muka Muka!
Muka Muka! What's wrong?
You can't swim, right?
Muka Muka!
Let's go to the island again.
Muka Muka and Muka together.
Muka Muka!
Are you all right?
I'm so nervous.
You guys.
Let's go back to the island.
I have a friend.
I don't have anything to do.
Let's go.
Muka Muka!
Let's swim again.
Who are you?
I'm still staying still.
Let's go to the Island.
Let's go to the island.
Is there a bird on the island?
Is there always a bird on the island?
Do you hear anything?
Is there a sound?
I'll be happy to see you again
Who's that old lady?
She's wearing a skirt on her face
Wow, so beautiful!
Can you give me this?
I'm so excited to see you again
But it's not bad, isn't it?
What?
Kyoryu and his parents are fighting?
That's how it is!
Next time on Mugamukapara Daiso,
I'll be looking forward to seeing you again in the next episode!